asiatees.com 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Atees.com

|  Thank you for accessing AsiaTees Hobbies Co. Ltd.("Atees.com", that's us). We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy.   
---  
This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.  
**We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any non-Atees.com web site to which this Site links or that links to this Site.**  
**Information Collection and Use**  
**1.** | **Information Collection.**  
---|---  
| We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to: help make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once; help you quickly find information, products, and services; help us create content on this Site that is most relevant to you; alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.   
a. | Email Addresses. Several locations of the Site permit you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: to request us to notify you when we receive a new brand, new product style, or product size; to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers. Your participation is completely voluntary, so you have a choice whether to participate and disclose information to us.  
b. | Cookies. Like many sites, this Site employs cookies to speed your navigation of the Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your Site usage.  
|  | i. | Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of this Site. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. THIS SITE'S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFITRATE A USER'S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER'S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. Our cookies are not "spyware."  
---|---  
c. | Product Reviews. You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we will ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location will be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private) . Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.  
**2.** | **Information Use and Disclosure.**  
a. | Internal Use. We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve our Site's content and layout, to improve our outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.   
b. | Communications with You: We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our site and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to request us to notify you when we receive a new brand, new product style, or product size; to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver the information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails (see the opt out section, below, for more details). Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders.  
c. | External Use. We want to provide you with excellent service and to offer you a great selection \- we primarily sell merchandise, not information. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone, except that:   
|  | i. | As do most catalog and Internet retailers, we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf. When we disclose information to these service providers, we disclose information to help them to perform their service. For example, in order to deliver products to you, we must share some information. We partner with third parties (such as the Hong Kong Post Office) to ship products, to ensure delivery, and so that we can obtain feedback, improve the quality of our service, and measure and improve the quality of the service of the third party. In the example of shippers, we provide them some personally identifiable information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number.   
---|---  
ii. | We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business.   
iii. | We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any user.  
---  
**Data Security**  
This Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for all financial transactions through this Site. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information.  
**OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS**  
Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address. You can make these requests by emailing to us. Please do not email your credit-card number or other sensitive information.  
**Update to this Policy**  
If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated.
